Narrator: 1
M: I live in New York.
Speaker: He
M: He lives in New York.
Narrator: 2
F: I finish work at eight.
Speaker: She
F: She finishes work at eight.
Narrator: 3
M: I teach English.
Speaker: My brother
M: My brother teaches English.
Narrator: 4
F: I watch CNN.
Speaker: She
F: She watches CNN.
Narrator: 5
M: I write books.
Speaker: He
M: He writes books.
Narrator: 6
F: I go to university.
Speaker: John
F: John goes to university.
Narrator: 7
M: I don’t eat meat.
Speaker: My sister
M: My sister doesn’t eat meat.
Narrator: 8
F: I don’t read newspapers.
Speaker: My husband
F: My husband doesn’t read newspapers.
Narrator: 9
M: Do you work?
Speaker: He
M: Does he work?
Narrator: 10
F: Do you drink coffee?
Speaker: She
F: Does she drink coffee?